hsv-k12.org 2019-03-14

# Huntsville City Schools Website Privacy Policy | Huntsville City Schools

Huntsville City Schools is committed to protecting your online privacy.  Any information provided to us through the Huntsville City Schools website such as email address, name, or phone number will never be sold or traded to other schools, nonprofit organizations, or businesses without your consent.  Huntsville City Schools might use this information to contact you about information or requests you have made using our web services.

###### Information Gathered Automatically

Unless you take steps to browse the internet anonymously, the Huntsville City Schools website tracks browsing patterns to inform the district about how our websites are being used.  These patterns are tracked by using generic information that may be collected using “cookies,” which are text files placed on your computer.  The use of these files can be blocked by using appropriate browser settings, however this may result in a loss of functionality on Huntsville City Schools websites.  Information the website collects in this way is based on your IP address, which identifies your network location and does not include other personally identifiable information unless provided directly by the user (E.g. Filling out an online form).

Huntsville City Schools websites utilize Google Analytics, a service provided by Google, Inc., to analyze how users interact with our sites.  Information used for this process is transmitted and stored by Google on its servers.  In some rare cases, Google may transfer this information to third parties where required to do so by law.  Google does not associate your IP address with any other personally identifiable data.  For more information about the information that is shared, visit Google’s [terms of service](https://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/terms/) and [privacy policy](https://www.google.com/policies/privacy/) pages.

###### Information Provided by End-Users

In order to allow Huntsville City Schools to communicate effectively with individuals using our websites, we may ask for personally identifiable information such as name, email address, or phone number.  Huntsville City Schools will never sell or trade personally identifiable information that is voluntarily provided unless consent is provided, or the district is required to do so by law.

###### External Content

Some parts of the Huntsville City Schools website may contain links to external websites which are not owned by or officially affiliated with Huntsville City Schools.  Huntsville City Schools is not responsible for the privacy practices or content of these external websites in any way.

###### More Information

For more information, or to contact us about any questions regarding this privacy statement, please use the [Website Feedback Form](https://www.huntsvillecityschools.org/website-feedback).
